

EMPLOYMENT

Freelance Designer 2015 - Present

CITY OF ORINDA

(Orinda, California)

Designed direct mailer for Recreation and Summer Camp Fair, in collaboration with Recreation Manager. Additionally, designed and developed a template for Display Board graphics which successfully reflected the overall look of the Orinda Activity Guide.

Program Specialist / Graphic Designer 2013 - Present

TOWN OF DANVILLE PARKS AND RECREATION

(Danville, California)

Spearheading efforts in designing various print material to liaise the Town of Danville with its residents through flyers, posters, newsletters, brochures, logos and t-shirts, which are original, yet in accordance with city's public image.

Freelance Designer 2013 - Present

IRVIN PR

(Columbus, Ohio)

Designed flyers, ads, logos, posters, and powerpoint presentations, turning subject matters into original final products.

Notable clients:

- Max & Ermas, Columbus Marathon, Star Lanes Polaris, Charity Newsies and Friends of Schiller Park.

Graphic Designer 2013 - 2014

HUE + BLURB CREATIVE

(Columbus, Ohio and Dublin, CA)

Delivered various design products for small to medium sized businesses including logos, website content, business cards and flyers, as well as development of brand identity.

Notable clients:

- Baby Steps Working Mom Life Coaching, Bolinger Retirement Solutions and Sammy's New York Bagels.

Store Artist 2005 - 2012

WHOLE FOODS MARKET

(Dublin, Ohio)

In collaboration with the Store Marketing Director contributed to the development of strong brand identity and increased brand awareness level by designing and creating department signage, chalkboards, print calendar of events, brochures, posters, large format signage, t-shirt designs, reusable bag designs and print advertising, which were successfully received by the customers.

- Additionally, trained 6 Store Artists on developing communication tools for better interaction with customers and team members in a dynamic environment.

Freelance Designer 2010

EDIBLE COLUMBUS

(Columbus, Ohio)

Created postcard to introduce Edible Columbus to the local vendor/producer community.

SUMMARY

Resourceful and energetic design savvy with more than 10 years of experience in delivering original final products which are in line with clients needs, successfully utilizing both artistic and technical side of this vocation. Regarded for reliability and strong communication skills. With the ability to work on multiple projects while still paying apt attention to details, acquired experience will be of great value to the company that can recognize these attributes.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts at Northern Kentucky University, 2001-2005

Major: Graphic Design

Area of Concentration: Marketing

SOFTWARE

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe InDesign

Adobe Photoshop

Quark XPress

Microsoft Word

FileMaker Pro

Microsoft Powerpoint

OPERATING SYSTEMS

Mac and Windows

LANGUAGES

Fully bilingual in English and Spanish

CONTACT



www.isabelbolinger.com Website



isabel.bolinger@gmail.com Email